<consent>
    <configuration>
        <messages>
            <message language="en">
                By clicking below, I represent and agree that I have read and agree to the Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy. I hereby
                agree and authorise the collection of biometric identifiers about me for the employment-related
                 authentication purposes and limited duration set out in the Privacy Policy.
            </message>
            <message language="cz">
                Kliknutím níže vyjadřuji svůj souhlas s tím, že jsem si přečetl/a smluvní podmínky použití a zásady ochrany osobních údajů. Tímto
                vyjadřují souhlas se shromažďováním biometrických identifikačních údajů týkajících se mé osoby, a to včetně identifikačních údajů ve
                formě otisků prstů a rozpoznávání tváře, pro účely ověření v rámci pracovního poměru a po dobu trvání stanovenou zásadami ochrany
                osobních údajů a toto shromažďování povoluji.
            </message>
            <message language="da">
                Ved at klikke nedenfor erklærer og accepterer jeg, at jeg har læst og accepterer brugsvilkårene og -betingelserne og
                privatlivspolitikken. Jeg accepterer og godkender hermed indsamlingen af biometriske identifikatorer om mig, herunder fingeraftryk og
                ansigtsgenkendelsesidentifikatorer, til de ansættelsesrelaterede godkendelsesformål og den begrænsede varighed, der er angivet i
                privatlivspolitikken.
            </message>
            <message language="de">
                Durch Klicken auf die Schaltfläche unten erkläre ich, dass ich die Nutzungsbedingungen und die Datenschutzrichtlinie gelesen habe und
                damit einverstanden bin. Hiermit stimme ich der Erfassung biometrischer Identifikationsmerkmalen über mich, einschließlich
                Fingerabdruck- und Gesichtserkennungsidentifikatoren, für die in der Datenschutzrichtlinie dargelegten arbeitnehmerbezogenen
                Authentifizierungszwecke und für eine begrenzte Dauer zu und genehmige diese.
            </message>
            <message language="es">
                Al hacer clic a continuación, declaro que he leído y acepto los Términos y condiciones de uso y la Regla de privacidad. Por la
                presente, acepto y autorizo la recopilación de identificadores biométricos sobre mí, incluidos identificadores de huellas dactilares y
                reconocimiento facial, para fines de autentificación relacionados con el empleo y duración limitada establecida en la Regla de
                privacidad.
            </message>
            <message language="fi">
                Napsauttamalla alta vahvistan lukeneeni ja hyväksyväni käyttöehdot sekä tietosuojakäytännön. Hyväksyn ja valtuutan biometristen
                tunnistustietojeni keräämisen, mukaan lukien sormenjälki- ja kasvojentunnistustiedot, työsuhteeseen liittyviin valtuutustarkoituksiin
                rajoitetun ajan tietosuojakäytännössä kuvatulla tavalla.
            </message>
            <message language="fr">
                En cliquant ci-dessous, je confirme avoir lu et approuvé les conditions générales d’utilisation et la politique de confidentialité.
                J’accepte et autorise par la présente la collecte de mes identifiants biométriques, notamment mes empreintes digitales et ma
                reconnaissance faciale, à des fins d’authentification dans le cadre de mon emploi et pour la durée limitée spécifiée dans la politique
                de confidentialité.
            </message>
            <message language="it">
                Cliccando di seguito, rappresento e accetto di aver letto i Termini e Condizioni della Policy di Utilizzo e Privacy. Con la presente
                accetto e autorizzo la raccolta di dati biometrici identificatori su di me, comprese impronte digitali e identificatori di
                riconoscimento facciale, per scopi di identificazione legati al lavoro e con durata limitata stabilita nella Policy sulla Privacy.
            </message>
            <message language="no">
                Ved å klikke nedenfor representerer og samtykker jeg i at jeg har lest og godtatt bruksvilkårene og retningslinjene for personvern.
                Jeg godtar herved og autoriserer innsamling av biometriske identifikatorer om meg, deriblant fingeravtrykk og identifikatorer for
                ansiktsgjenkjenning, for de sysselsettingsrelaterte godkjenningsformålene og den begrensede varigheten som er fastsatt i
                retningslinjene for personvern.
            </message>
            <message language="nl">
                Door hieronder te klikken bevestig ik dat ik de Algemene Gebruiksvoorwaarden en het Privacybeleid heb gelezen en ermee akkoord ga. Ik
                ga akkoord met de inzameling van biometrische identificatiemiddelen bedoeld voor arbeidsgerelateerde
                 authenticatie en gedurende de beperkte periode zoals uiteengezet in het Privacybeleid.
            </message>
            <message language="pl">
                Klikając poniżej, oświadczam, że przeczytałem/-am i zgadzam się z Warunkami korzystania z tej platformy i Polityką prywatności.
                Niniejszym wyrażam zgodę i zezwalam na pozyskanie danych biometrycznych o mnie, w tym odcisków palców i elementów rozpoznawania
                twarzy, w celach uwierzytelnienia związanych z zatrudnieniem i na czas określony w Polityce prywatności.
            </message>
            <message language="pt">
                Ao clicar abaixo, confirmo que li e concordo com os Termos e Condições de Utilização e a Regra de Privacidade. Pelo presente concordo
                e autorizo a recolha de identificadores biométricos sobre mim, incluindo impressões digitais e reconhecimento facial, para fins de
                autenticação relacionada com o emprego e duração limitada definida na Regra de Privacidade.
            </message>
            <message language="se">
                Genom att klicka nedan, intygar och medger jag att jag har läst och samtycker till Användarvillkoren och Sekretesspolicyn. Jag
                samtycker härmed till och godkänner insamlingen av biometriska identifierare om mig, inklusive identifierare av fingeravtryck och
                ansiktsigenkänning, för de anställningsrelaterade autentiseringsändamålen och den begränsade varaktighet som anges i Sekretesspolicyn.
            </message>
        </messages>
        <expiryTimeInDays>365</expiryTimeInDays>
        <daysToGiveWarning>30</daysToGiveWarning>
    </configuration>
    <signature />
</consent>
